<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Datatable xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CircusesAndBreadTitle">Circuses and Bread</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CircusesAndBreadDescription">News has reached your citizens' ears of great achievements, great expeditions, and great discoveries -- performed by other empires. Envy has seized their hearts, and you feel their discontent growing with every distant success spoken of in bustling markets and heaving caravanserai across the empire. They need to be made proud of their own empire's successes -- or, more straightforwardly, distracted from hard truths through gluttony and spectacle.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CircusesAndBreadObjective">Calm unhappy citizens with a period of feasts and festivities.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CircusesAndBread-Step1">Produce at least 12 of Food \7700\ and Influence \7704\ in your city $CityName for a period of 5 turns $Progression</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CircusesAndBread-Step1Tooltip">You can work with Population, Luxuries, and Improvements to achieve this.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CircusesAndBread-Step2" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CircusesAndBread-Step2Tooltip" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CircusesAndBreadOutcome">The citizens have been sated on delicacies and entertainments, their envy forgotten. Bravo!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWarTitle">Make Dust Not War</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWarDescription">A connoisseur of Auriga's rare marvels, luxury delicacies, and Endless paraphernalia, the leader of the $MinorFaction is willing to ally with you on one strict condition: you prove your talent in the marketplace, demonstrating to them that they will enjoy plenty of interesting trinkets if they tie their fortunes to your empire. One day they even dream of finding relics associated with the legendary Eslek Tarosh, the mysterious being who appears on the Day of the Awakening. They can hope.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWarObjective">Prove yourself an adept marketplace trader to convince the $MinorFaction to join your ranks.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWar-Step1">Successfully sign 3 peace trades with other major factions in the next $Timer turns. $Progression.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWar-Step1Tooltip">In the Diplomacy Screen you can find information about Trades. For these Trades you need to unlock the 'Diplomat's Manse' (Era 2) technology.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWar-Step2" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWar-Step2Tooltip" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWarOutcome">The leader of the $MinorFaction is most impressed with your adroitness in the market, and looks forward to a profitable relationship.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWarRewardTitle">$MinorFaction Pacification</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MakeDustNotWarRewardDescription">Once you have made the 3 peaceful trades, the Minor Faction will join your Empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter1WhoGoesThere_Title">Chapter 1: Who Goes There?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter1WhoGoesThere_Description">Deep in the heart of the temple complex, an advance scout party from your army discover the archaeologist. That's what they call him on account of the tools and instruments they found in his possession, as he lay wounded, breathing hard, on the stone ground. He says he is a Vaulter by the name of Llic Zoltan, claims wild animals attacked him while exploring.
 
Whether you believe him or not, he recounts an incredible tale about his distant ancestors hailing from the stars, about how a great Vaulter vessel crashed onto the world centuries ago. Unlike his kin he is convinced other starfaring vessels still exist on Auriga -- and says that by finding the the traces of their explosive departures, he can find the vessels themselves...
 
He says he is willing to share the fruits of his labor if you will help with his next expedition. He believes he is close, but the expedition will not be easy and needs many provisions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter1WhoGoesThere_Objective">A stranger, Llic Zoltan, believes starfaring vessels still exist on Auriga and wants to track the scars left by their departures. Prepare for an expedition by assembling necessary provisions.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter1WhoGoesThere_Step1">Increase $LuxuryName to $LuxuryAmount .</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter1WhoGoesThere_Step1Tooltip">Luxury Resources can be collected by building Extractors, or purchased on the Market.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter1WhoGoesThere_Outcome">Success! Llic cast a careful eye over the supplies, his stern face finally segueing into a broad grin. We are going to make history, he tells you.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter2TheToolForTheJob_Title">Chapter 2: Under a Starlight Sky</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter2TheToolForTheJob_Description">Llic's enthusiasm for the forthcoming expedition is infectious. Even if he's pursuing a fantasy, you can't doubt his sincerity, nor his energy. Among the soldiers chosen to accompany the Vaulter you can feel an excitement, a feeling that they have a real purpose, one that might change everything.
 
Although you shouldn't, sometimes you indulge the dream too. Llic has weaved magical words about the stars, how each point of light among the millions in the silky black night sky is a chance of a fertile world where your people could be truly free.
 
Llic has identified two sites of Endless ruins that show the effects of the great forces that would have been required to lift a ship into the sky. He is convinced that vindication is near...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter2TheToolForTheJob_Objective">The Vaulter Llic is convinced he is close to discovering an ancient Endless launchpad. Mount the necessary expeditions under appropriate leadership.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter2TheToolForTheJob_Step1">Investigate two more Ruins on land with a Hero-led army $Progression </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter2TheToolForTheJob_Step1Tooltip">Make sure that the exploring Army is led by a Hero!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter2TheToolForTheJob_Outcome">The digs unearthed copious valuable materials, a large cache of Endless writings, but of a vessel capable of traveling the stars there is no sign. Llic is furious.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter3OriginOfTheEvil_Title">Chapter 3: A Man Possessed</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter3OriginOfTheEvil_Description">For such an academic, learned man, you'd never have guessed that Llic could work himself up into such a rage. That first night, when the expedition had explored every last antechamber in the scorched Endless ruins, when the soldiers sat exhausted from all the debris they'd cleared, when not an inkling of a so-called 'starship' materialized, Llic's animal cries of frustration echoed through the entire ruins.
 
The next day his serenity returned. And his fire. A setback, he called the expeditions, nothing more. With the new Endless writings uncovered, together with his old research, he was certain new leads would be discovered. The Endless were spacefaring gods, he says. The destruction throughout this ruin could only have been from successive launches of giant vessels.
 
He calls for your renewed aid, pleads that as you have come this far with him, you must not abandon him now. He will need researchers, linguists, workshops, and more besides, but the prize will be great.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter3OriginOfTheEvil_Objective">Llic believes the new Endless writings still hold the key to locating a launch site and a star vessel. Provide him with the necessary scientific support.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter3OriginOfTheEvil_Step1">Increase your empire science output by 45. </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter3OriginOfTheEvil_Step1Tooltip">Increase science.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter3OriginOfTheEvil_Outcome">Eureka! The intense research of the Endless writings has led to the reconstruction of an ancient device: a transmitting 'key' that has opened a secret bunker in the earlier ruins…</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter4OldVoices_Title">Chapter 4: Old Haunts</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter4OldVoices_Description">After so many years of searching, Llic cannot contain his excitement. Nobody, he believes, has ever resurrected Endless technology before, even if that technology is, essentially, nothing more complex than a simple key to a door. But what lies behind that door is most intriguing...
 
The Vaulter is sure all his prayers will be answered in that deep crypt, but other voices counsel that the archeologist is making a leap of faith, that he is seeing order where there is only chaos. Others suggest that the secret bunker may indeed hold remains of the Endless, but not anything as grand as a starship.
 
Your advisors also caution that it is not infeasible that ancient defensive forces may be triggered by any approach. Bringing a strong military force would be prudent.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter4OldVoices_Objective">The Vaulter's tireless work has born... What? Nobody knows yet. It is time to explore the secret Endless bunker -- with a sufficiently powerful army should its defense mechanisms still be functional.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter4OldVoices_Step1">Return to the previously explored Ruin.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter4OldVoices_Step1Tooltip">The army will have to fight, so make sure it is strong and healthy.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter4OldVoices_Step2">Defend the ruin for $Progression \7708\ Turns. Every 2 \7708\ Turns a new enemy Army will spawn and will attack you. At least one of your Armies must remain in the same Region as the Ruin and stay within 3 tiles of it.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter4OldVoices_Step2Tooltip">At least one of your Armies must stay within 3 tiles distance from the Ruin</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Chapter4OldVoices_Outcome">Llic is stunned to tears. These ruins were damaged not by ships departing, but by weapons fired from somewhere else in the cosmos. Llic demands a moment alone, and steps out of the bunker. He is never seen again. The mysterious questions he unearthed remain, however. Who would shoot at a planet, not simply destroy it, and why?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_LegendsOfOld_Title">Legends Of Old</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_LegendsOfOld_Description">Archeological pieces deciphered by some of the empire's foremost authorities on the Endless have revealed something most intriguing -- and tempting. They suggest that the impenetrable security systems guarding a rare Endless artifact at an Aurigan ruins will soon be disabled for a fixed period of time. That's the good news. The bad news is that the evidence is ambiguous as regards to the exact location of the ruins, with two sites being prime candidates. Worse, the wrong site is most likely to trigger aggressive defense forces if explored...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_LegendsOfOld_Objective">One of two possible ruins holds a lot of dust and a talisman of immense power. The other only enemies. Find the artifact.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_LegendsOfOld_Step1">Within the next $Timer \7708\ turns, explore the correct ruin and get the reward you seek.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_LegendsOfOld_Step1Tooltip">The Ruins will be indicated with a Ray of Dust</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_LegendsOfOld_Outcome">The archeologists were right! The artifact is a sight to behold, the craftsmanship otherworldly, and soon, no doubt likely to be adorning one very privileged individual.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Infestation_Title">Cooperative: Infestation!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Infestation_Description">The Urkans -- Kazar, Chaka, and Fakir -- have risen from the depths of the earth, making the ground quake with their every stride, and striking fear into the hearts of every Aurigan. Their minions, the aggressive lice that emerged with them, are terrorizing ordinary folk, and threaten to run rampage over the entire land. All empires have agreed this infestation needs a collective response, and have committed to eliminating as many of the lice as they can. As a reward to encourage participation in the hunt, the empires have agreed that the empire with the best number of kills will enjoy a handsome bounty.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Infestation_Objective">Peace across all lands is threatened! The Urkan's despised lice must be eradicated without prejudice.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Infestation_Step1">Kill more Urkan Lice than any other empires. $Progression.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Infestation_Step1Tooltip">The Lice could appear in a Region which has at least one Ruin.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Infestation_Outcome">The hunt is over! Dozens of the dreaded lice lay dead, while the only ones who mourn their passing are the behemoths from whence they came.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Infestation_Step1RewardTitle">The major contributor will win dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Infestation_Step1RewardDescription">The Reward depends on the number of Urkan Lice killed by each Empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CityGoneRogue_Title">Global Competitive: City Gone Rogue</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CityGoneRogue_Description">What strange beast is this?! It appears that a Roving Clans city has been seized by some sort of madness and is off on a bloody rampage. Imagine, an entire mobile city, full of houses and people, gone out of control. Reports come in from across the planet of the confusion and devastation that the thing has left behind it; the beast must be stopped before even more damage is done.
 
All the empires of Auriga are welcome in this effort! And with luck, whoever manages to dominate the Setseke may even get use of it...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CityGoneRogue_Objective">To arms! Stop the rampaging Setseke before it can spread more ruin and cause more tears.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CityGoneRogue_Outcome">Victory! Becalmed and docile -- and heavily wounded -- the Setseke seems to once again be under the control of its masters. And even better, those masters are now under your control. The city is yours!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CityGoneRogue_Step">Defeat the Setseke in battle.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CityGoneRogue_StepTooltip">The Setseke has appeared in some region with a ruin.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CityGoneRogue_RewardTitle">The control of the Setseke</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_CityGoneRogue_RewardDescription">The Setseke is carrying a whole City for you!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_Title">Cooperative: A Land of Fire and Ash</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_Description">What dark sorcery is this? On the far horizon, a black peak riven with fire spews an ashen rain across the surrounding terrain, threatening to permenantly turn good land into blackened wasteland. Reports have it that these artificial monstrosities are scattered across the whole of Auriga, always springing up in empty places, far from major cities.
 
Who seeded such destructive mechanisms? To what end? These are vital questions, but not our focus at this time. Now, we must marshal our power -- collectively, as Aurigans united! -- to destroy as many of these wicked machines before our lands are scorched beyond hope.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_Objective">Auriga's pristine lands must be protected! Destroy the barbaric terraforming machinery before the world becomes a volcanic hellscape.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_Outcome">The land is saved...well, at least the majority of it. What might've become basalt plains and volcanic lakes is still largely grassland and forest and scrub. Aurigans of all races and means are thankful for the intervention.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_Step">Destroy as many Volcanoformers as possible before they cause irreversible damage. $Progression.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_StepTooltip">Your Army has a Dismantle action for deactivating the devices.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_StepRewardDescription">Global and per participant reward (podium).</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_StepRewardTitle">Remove: \7806\  -1 on City Food production</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%QuestWorldEffect#0011AddedTitle">Volcanic ash</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%QuestWorldEffect#0011AddedDescription">Due volcanic ash falling from sky, tiles are producing less food.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%QuestWorldEffect#0011RemovedTitle">Food production back to normal</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%QuestWorldEffect#0011RemovedDescription">The deactivation of the volcanoformers devices normalized food production.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_PerContributionRewardTitle">Per Contribution: $RewardPerContribution</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_Volcanoformers_PerContributionRewardDescription">Total received for each of your contribution once quest completed.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WinterCelebrations_Title">Celebrating the Solstice</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WinterCelebrations_Description">Aurigan winters are feared for their length and intensity. Much of an empire's effort during the other seasons must go into planning for winter's arrival or mitigating its effects.
 
This time, why not try something different? Consider making winter a time of festivities, a time when families and communities come together, a time when shared values and experiences are celebrated. Enough of these dark moods that mirror the dark skies! Perhaps it might be better to shower your hard-working citizens in luxuries, giving them a bit of cheer to last through these frozen months.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WinterCelebrations_Objective">Activate Luxury Resource boosters to invigorate your citizens with a bit of joy during the winter months.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WinterCelebrations_Outcome">Rejoice! Productivity and morale have improved, and celebrations across the empire have removed much of the doom and gloom of the season. The hangovers, I'm sure you agree, are a small price to pay.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WinterCelebrations_Step1">Before the end of this winter, have at least $AmountLocale luxury boosts active. $Progression.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WinterCelebrations_Step1Tooltip">Luxury Resource boosters can be activated from the empire screen.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MajesticCreatures_Title">Majestic Creatures</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MajesticCreatures_Description">You may not have seen or heard of them, but one of the greatest marvels of Auriga's diverse wildlife is the stunning Skyfin. They have been called flying carpets, lizard angels, floating dreams, and many odder things. Famed not only for their beauty but also their rapid movement and their ability to harvest strategic resources, any leader of an empire would want one under their command.
 
Luck, it seems, is with you; a Skyfin has been spotted moving alone across the wilds of Auriga. Perhaps it can be yours!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MajesticCreatures_Objective">Capture this gorgeous creature and make it your own!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MajesticCreatures_Outcome">Whether or not you are a collector of exotic pets, to have something both gorgeous and practical is a rare occurrence. Congratulations on your good fortune!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MajesticCreatures_Step1">Defeat the Skyfin seen at $RegionNameLocale within $Timer \7708\ turns.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MajesticCreatures_Step1Tooltip">Be the first Empire to capture this marvelous creature!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MajesticCreatures_RewardTitle">You gain control of the Skyfin.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_MajesticCreatures_RewardDescription">The Skyfin can absorb Resources for your Empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Title">A Helpless Hero</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Description">The ruins of Auriga are perilous places, even for those who wield exceptional powers. A courier has arrived with a message from a distant land, reporting that a mysterious figure has been trapped in some sort of disaster at one of the Endless's ruins. Furthermore, the being in question appears to be one of the Dust-wielding Heroes, given that they had been moving large masses of rock in an attempt to work their way out.
 
Fascinating. Another Hero among your officers and administrators could only be advantageous -- though if they are wounded, the trip may not be easy...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Objective">Recruit another Hero to your ranks by exploring the indicated Ruins, then escorting them to one of your cities.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Outcome">A good deed that has been well rewarded. It may take some time for them to recover, but it is likely that this Hero will have far more value to you than the time and effort that was invested in their rescue.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Step1">Reach the ruin marked on the map, join the hero to your ranks.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Step2">With your army take the wounded hero to the marked city to recover before $Timer \7708\ turns.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Step2Tooltip">Once in the City, you can transfer the army to the Hero, or keep it for one \7708\ Turn in the City. After that, you will have to wait several \7708\ Turns until the Hero is healed and can be assigned.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Step1Tooltip">Be the first Empire to reach the indicated Ruin.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Step1RewardTitle">Honorific Title</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Step1RewardDescription">Only one Empire will have the honor of having helped the Hero. The Army will be renamed as 'Rescuers of the Hero'.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Step2RewardTitle">A wounded Hero</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_Step2RewardDescription">Once completed, you will find the wounded Hero in the Hero Screen.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AForgottenHero_ArmyName">Rescuers of the Hero</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WeTakeFromTheLand_Title">Unnatural Resources</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WeTakeFromTheLand_Description">It seems that a group of "freelance entrepreneurs" (Note: pirates and brigands) wants to come clean. However, they need a justification to convince their followers that it makes sense to adopt a sedentary, low-risk lifestyle, and they are wondering if your empire might help.
 
They would be happy to operate your resource extraction sites -- which are generally far from prying eyes -- if you open enough sites for them to bring in their kith and kin. In addition, they will throw in a bit of their ill-gained booty as a thank you for giving them a second chance.
 
After all, there are many keys to wealth and power on Auriga, but harvesting the abundant natural resources is one of the best. Why not gain a bit more, and return some stolen booty to the imperial coffers?</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WeTakeFromTheLand_Objective">Before they change their mind, build additional Strategic Resource Extractors to help a gang of outlaws find a new life.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WeTakeFromTheLand_Outcome">Well, that worked out better than expected! A little something in the treasury, one less threat to the good people of your empire, and more resources pouring in. It's so nice when a plan comes together.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WeTakeFromTheLand_Step1">Before $Timer \7708\ turns, get 2 more strategic extractors within your empire $Progression.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WeTakeFromTheLand_Step1Tooltip">You need to place them on unexploited Strategic Resource lodes.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_WeTakeFromTheLand_RewardTitle" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_TheirBackWasTurned_Title">Surprise Party!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_TheirBackWasTurned_Description">An infamous political philosopher once posited that "the ends justify the means". While there is great debate over the morality of this statement, there are certainly times when that sort of pragmatic approach can be useful.
 
Consider your friends and allies for instance. Are they really that helpful? Are they really that useful? Or could one of them, perhaps, be sacrificed on the unholy altar of political expediency?
 
The decision is yours, of course. But remember that you do still have to look in the mirror the next day...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_TheirBackWasTurned_Objective">Turn a less useful ally into a useful enemy -- and take out a few of their armies as well.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_TheirBackWasTurned_Step1">Declare war or cold war on an Ally or break a truce.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_TheirBackWasTurned_Step1Tooltip">Declare war or cold war on an Ally or break a truce.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_TheirBackWasTurned_Step2">Defeat 3 armies of that faction before $Timer turns $Progression.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_TheirBackWasTurned_Step2Tooltip">You have to be mean, and you have to be fast!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_TheirBackWasTurned_Outcome">What's done is done! One can only hope that the ally in question was a double-crossing fink who was considering doing the same thing to you.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_RampagingGolems_Title">A Gaggle of Golems</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_RampagingGolems_Description">An emperor is used to hearing requests for help, but this is a new one. Some sort of fire-wielding constructs appear to be ravaging the countryside, and your surprised and somewhat scorched populace is demanding that you get rid of them. More than merely your own people, a small village of $MinorFaction have been particularly hard hit by this incursion.
 
A few questions in the right places tells you that these Kapaku golems are indeed masters of fire and lava; it's about time to get them away from crops, wooden buildings, and barns full of hay. The $MinorFaction will in fact be more than happy to pledge their support to your empire if you show them that you can put out the fires and put down the instigators.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_RampagingGolems_Objective">Assist the $MinorFaction by getting rid of the rampaging Kapaku golems.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_RampagingGolems_Outcome">Your people breathe a sigh of relief, as temperaments and temperatures get back to normal. The $MinorFaction is happy to join with you, seeing that you know how to deal with the unusual and unexpected.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_RampagingGolems_Step1">Defeat the Kapaku army that has been seen wandering in the vicinity of the $RegionLocale region.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_RampagingGolems_Step1Tooltip">You will need a strong Army to defeat it.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_RampagingGolems_RewardTitle">$MinorFaction Pacification</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_RampagingGolems_RewardDescription">The $MinorFaction will join your Empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AMeltingPotOfPower_Title">Forged in the Melting Pot</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AMeltingPotOfPower_Description">Your strategic advisors counsel you, in hushed and embarrassed tones, that your military strategies have become… predictable. Predictable! That's almost as bad as boring! What can you do to make your battlefield presence a bit less by-the-numbers, and your enemies a bit less efficient?
 
Your Deputy for Imperial Diversity has a recommendation: Recruit additional Minor Faction peoples into your empire, and use their unusual and often powerful tactics in your battles. Change your line-up, and alter your abilities. Hmmmm. Now there is a suggestion that might just make the neighbors think twice when they decide to send troops rolling in your direction. And all the more surprising that it came from an in-law, generally regarded as useless, for whom you had to invent the job and the title...</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AMeltingPotOfPower_Objective">Ensure that your Cities have population from pacified Minor Faction villages.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AMeltingPotOfPower_Outcome">So far morale seems to be fine, and the diversity of your cities has had surprisingly little trouble. That might even merit a promotion from "Deputy" to "Counselor"…</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AMeltingPotOfPower_Step1">Have at least 5 cities with at least 1 population from pacified villages.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AMeltingPotOfPower_Step1Tooltip">Minor Factions can be pacified by quests, the use of dust, or defeating them in battle.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AMeltingPotOfPower_RewardTitle">$MinorFaction Pacification</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_AMeltingPotOfPower_RewardDescription">The $MinorFaction will join your Empire</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_Title">Thunder Below</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_Description">Something is going on, and it's down where you can't see it. Several towns are reporting vibrations and rumbles, as if boulders are grinding against each other beneath the ground. The other, more likely explanation is that some Urkan "lice" are getting restless. The problem, however, is that villages are going sleepless, the herd animals are spooked, and children are terrified. In other words, something has to be done.
 
Experts and alchemists agree that the lice can be tempted out of their lairs by offerings of tasty and exotic luxuries; it seems like an odd solution, but anything is better than hearing all that complaining. Who knows? Maybe you'll even learn to live with them.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_Objective">Tempt the roaming lice out of their lairs and get rid of them!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_Step1">Deposit $LuxuryAmount $LuxuryName in the Ruins indicated by a ray of light.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_Step1Tooltip">Luxury Resources can be harvested with Extractors or purchased on the Marketplace</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_Step2">Defeat the roaming lice armies in $Region1Name and $Region2Name. $Progression</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_Step2Tooltip">Defeat the roaming lice armies.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_Outcome">Now that's something different. You not only have gained a bit of peace and the gratitude of your people, but some of the more risk-prone soldiers are learning to fight alongside these Lice. Auriga remains as defiantly odd as ever.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_RewardTitle">Urkan Lice Army</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_SoundsFromBelow_RewardDescription">You gain control of a 3 Urkan Lice Army.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_Title">Wildfire</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_Description">They say that some like it hot. But nobody of sound mind likes it quite this hot. A Fire Guardian, perhaps driven mad in the chains and dungeons of the Endless, is reported to be heading towards your realms. These powerful elementals are frightening as enemies and useful as allies; who knows what might come of this encounter?
 
It seems there are two ways of dealing with the threat -- outright military destruction, or simple pacification (better known as "bribery"). Whichever path you choose, let's hope you can smother the threat!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_Objective">Defeat the Fire Guardian in combat, or gather enough Titan Bones to pacify them.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_Step1">Activate 5 Titan bones Boosters in the next $Timer turns, $Progression</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_Step1Tooltip" />
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_Step2">Defeat the Guardian</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_Step2Tooltip">They are very large and very strong. Good luck!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_Outcome">A cheer goes up! The danger has been averted, peace restored, and all those who live in wooden dwellings are particularly appreciative.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_RewardTitle">Guardian of Fire</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_ARagingFire_RewardDescription">Control of the Fire Guardian.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Title">Of Priests and Pirates</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Description">What new idiocy is sweeping across your territories? Some leader of outlaws has decided it is more effective to position themselves as a religious leader. And, that quickly, the Church of Worldly Gratification was created. Claiming that the act of collecting wealth shows proof of the collector being blessed and pure, all sorts of deserters, outcasts, and thieves are banding together in the guise of faith and devotion.
 
Enough of that! It's time to sort things out, chastize the recently-converted bandits, and let these charlatans know that they are not about to displace the loyalty due to the true leaders of empire.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Objective">Stamp out this cult of greed and hypocrisy by defeating the bands of thugs in the four highlighted locations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Step1">Go to the first ruin and defeat their defending army, 1/4.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Step1Tooltip">The Ruins that hide your enemies will be indicated on the map by rays of Dust.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Step2">Go to the second ruin and defeat their defending army, 2/4.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Step2Tooltip">Onward!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Step3">Go to the third ruin and defeat their defending army, 3/4.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Step3Tooltip">Good luck!</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Step4">Go to the fourth ruin and defeat their defending army, 4/4.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Step4Tooltip">The last one…</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21_BunkersOfMadness_Outcome">What an interesting collection of adversaries! Apparently some people will believe anything that a leader tells them, no matter how ridiculous it sounds. Tranquility has been restored, and your troops now have experience with a very wide range of opponents.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21PackTitle">Monstrous Tales</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21PackDescription">Monstrous Tales delivers a raft of new quest lines, including a separate and unusual multi-part adventure into ancient truths that are nothing less than... monstrous.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%DLC21PackLore">The 20 new tales are enriched with monsters and myths from the depths of Auriga's mysterious and menacing history; a tapestry of friends and foes, hope and horror.
Encounter the myriad strange representatives of civilizations -- occasionally quite uncivilized - as well as the other peoples, tribes, herds, and packs that inhabit and infest the wide reaches of Auriga.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WorldGeneratorScenarioDLC21Title">Auriga</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WorldGeneratorScenarioDLC21Content">Explore the vast lands of Auriga, conquer its boundless regions, and gain control of key strategic locations.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%WorldGeneratorScenarioDLC21Description">Explore the vast land of Auriga.</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName0">The Spice Islands</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName1">Qua'usk</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName2">Manyur</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName3">Ataiu</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName4">Western Narrow</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName5">Southern Narrow</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName6">Achq</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName7">Amenvar</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName8">The Boiling Peaks</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName9">The Whispering Galleries</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName10">Sam-risum</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName11">The Lookout Islands</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName12">Deepswater</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName13">Mulladien</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName14">Salt Sea</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName15">Table Mount</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName16">Ormn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName17">Marebond</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName18">Worimer</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName19">Valdaea</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName20">O'Irenth</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName21">Sipuan</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName22">Almed</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName23">Mapaa</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName24">Oddenda</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName25">Sea of Sorrows</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName26">Aduran</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName27">Zadde</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName28">Moch</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName29">Trenwin</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName30">Aberian</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName31">Whiechsul</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName32">Kentamys</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName33">The Vasts</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName34">Yaeg</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName35">Kalch</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName36">Suan</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName37">Cyin</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName38">Naillon</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName60">Dardogar</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName61">Adikin</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName62">Karrandar</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName63">Zhagorak</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName64">Beloch</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName65">Sliq</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName66">Yaeg</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName67">Undand</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName68">Endigir</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName69">Himun</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName70">Darklands</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName71">Agai</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName72">Lionith</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName73">Nolaran </LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName74">Shadonn</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName75">Strard</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName76">Trode</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName77">Omgar</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName79">Aldodev</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName82">Dhoyach</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName89">Shiamere</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName90">Ovoru</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName97">Ranf</LocalizationPair>
  <LocalizationPair Name="%AurigaRegionName99">Perusk</LocalizationPair>
</Datatable>